

SHIRONE FORTUNO

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

A passionate and dedicated Junior Software Engineer specializing in HTML, CSS, Javascript, Salesforce and Google Firebase with strong fundamentals in utilizing web development frameworks such as Tailwind and Bootstrap 5.

Have done several projects involving front and back end development.

04-645-848-09

+63-995-718-2778

 ${\color{red} \,\,{\textstyle igsigma}} \,\, {\color{blue} \,\,{\sf Shironebfortuno@gmail.com}}$

in Shirone Fortuno

https://github.com/shironeF

4108, Tanza, Cavite.

Education

Bachelor of Science in Information Technology

Cavite State University | 2012-2015 Undergraduate

Reference

Mr. BRYL LIM.

Co-founder & CEO of PocketDevs

bryllim@gmail.com

Work Experience

Customer Service Representative

SOW Philippines Fulfillment Inc. (PAYO) | 2019 - 2021

- Implement effective strategies to optimize successful deliveries of PAYO's partner merchants products.
- Answer all emails and calls to address customer concerns and expectations.
- Develop a strong professional business relationship as a key point of contact for the company between merchants and their clients.

Customer Service Representative

Call2Connect Solutions Inc. | 2016 - 2017

- Active engagement with clients in product launches and promotional campaigns
- Acquire new clients and increase business with existing customers.
- · Accelerate the growth of sales.

Project Experience

FoodPad v2 React, Tailwind, Google Firebase

Kodego - Full-Stack Web Development Bootcamp

- Food ordering website.
- Using API, administrators can log in and upload new products using an admin account in real time.
- Customers can place, add and remove orders which exhibits accurate sum and total quantity of orders placed in the cart.

Contributions

- Designing and Lavout.
- Database and API implementation.
- Log in system and User Authentication

FoodPad v1 HTML and CSS

Kodego - Full-Stack Web Development Bootcamp

- Static Food delivery service website that demonstrate original designs and aesthetics.
- Users can navigate through different pages of the web that demonstrate how a food delivery service be like.

Contributions

- · Designing and Layout
- · HTML and CSS coding

Skills

Front-end Back-end Database CRM

- HTML
- PHP
- MySQL
- Salesforce

CSS

- Firebase
- Javascript
- React